迷失前情提要...
Previously on "lost"...
有律师来找我
Some lawyers came to see me.
他们想知道Aaron是不是我儿子
They wanted to test to see if Aaron's my son.
你得解决这件事
You need to take care of them.
你会不惜一切保住Aaron吧
Wouldn't you do anything you had to in order to keep Aaron?
好啊  Kate
Hello, Kate.
他和我一起的
He's with me.
就是他要抢走Aaron
He's the one who's trying to take Aaron.
是我
It was me.
对不起
Sorry.
Charlotte!
我们得回到兰花站
We have to go back the orchid.
一切从那里开始  或许可以在那里结束
That's where all this started. maybe it's where it'll all stop.
发生这一切  是因为他们的离开
This is happening because they left.
如果我带他们回来  或许能阻止这一切
I think it'll stop if I can bring them back.
海面有人
un homme la mer!
-你叫什么?  -Jin
-What is your name? -Jin.
我是Danielle
I am Danielle.
Danielle Rousseau
喂?
Sun?  你在哪?
我还在洛杉矶
我快要做完事情了
明天我就坐飞机回来了
Ji Yeon要和你说话哦
妈妈
宝贝  告诉你
妈妈给你在美国找了个新朋友哦
他叫Aaron
妈妈快回家  我好想你哦
我很快就回来啦
宝贝  妈妈爱你哦
再见啦
为什么要骚扰我们母子?!
Why don't you leave me and my son alone?!
因为他不是你的儿子  Kate
Because he's not your son, Kate.
走开  Kate
Move away, Kate.
-Sun  -我说走开!
-Sun...-I said, move away!
-Sun! 你干嘛? Aaron在哪?  -车里
-S-sun! what are you doing? where's Aaron? -he's in the car.
Sun  我知道你以为你是在...
Sun, listen. I know you think you're helping...
如果不是你  Jin就不会死
If it wasn't for you, Jin would still be alive.
Sun  我没有杀死你丈夫
I didn't kill your husband, sun.
-你有  -不  我没有
-Yes, you did.  -No, I didn't.
没人杀害他  因为他没死
Neither did anyone else, because he's not dead.
你说谎
You're lying.
Sun  我没有
No, sun.
Jin还活着
Jin's still alive,
我能证明给你看
And I can prove it.
8, 15, 16, 23, 42.
8, 15...
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
你是Rousseau?
You Rousseau?
Danielle Rousseau?
是的  没错
Yes. th-that's right.
你从哪来的?
Where you from?
-我们从塔希提岛一路航行过来  -什么时候?
-We sailed from tahiti. -When?
11月15日
November 15th.
我是问哪一年?
No. what year?
1988年
1988.
怎么了?
Why?
怎么回事?
What's the matter?
我...
I...
我...我得去找到我的营地
I-i need go find my camp.
什么营地?
W-what camp?
你以前就在这岛上?
You were on this island before?
你看到直升机了吗?
You see helicopter?
先是船  现在又是直升机  待会你又要问...
我们有没有看到潜水艇了吧 ?
拜托  我知道该怎么走
你确定?
信号很强
岛上肯定有发射站
到了那  我们就能寻找帮助了
这岛上有发射站吗?
Is there an antenna on the island?
Jin  帮帮忙  这里...
Hey, Jin! is...uh, please.
是不是有...
Is there, um...
无线电发送站?
Ra...a radio tower?
好了
Okay.
就是这种
Like that.
这里是不是有个无线电发送站?
Is there a-a radio tower here?
是的
Yes.
可我必须找到我的营地  因为或许...
But i-i must find my camp because maybe, uh...
直升机去那里了
Helicopter go there.
你知道从这怎么去你的营地?
Do you know where your camp is from here?
不知道
No.
那知道怎么去无线发电站吗?
How about from the radio tower?
那一起去发电站  然后我们再找你的营地
Then go with us to the tower. then we'll find your camp.
好的
Okay.
那就这样  我们走吧
准备好出发了吗?
Are you ready to go?
好了
Yes.
你在找谁?
Who are you hoping to find?
我妻子
My wife.
这边
Danielle  怎么了
没什么
我就知道这样不对
你已经怀孕7个月了
Robert  我没事
她只是踢了我一下
-她?  -她!
我们还要说几次
Alexander是男孩
Alexandera肯定是女孩
在这休息一下吧
我去拿水
水呢
水壶在Nadine那里
Nadine?
Nadine!
带了女人就是麻烦
说不定她去捉蝴蝶了
你听到了吗?
Did you hear that?
什么东西?
What is that?
怪物
Monster.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视原创翻译制作
最新最快的美剧 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译： 七色九天 蚊子 小的瑟 rosemaryai
翻译： blackeyepea 牛牛  字幕总监：七色九天
■
后期： 梁良   校对：  许愿
谁最后一个见Nadine?
她一直在我后面的
好吧  我们回去找她
好  我们回去找她
Okay. we go find her.
不行  我们必须往前走
No. we must go.
你闭嘴
You shut up.
走
Allez.
Nadine!
Nadine! nadine!
大家分散开去找
她肯定就在附近
Brennan  Laconbe  你们去那边找
好的
Okay.
Nadine! nadine!
快跑!
Run!
那是什么鬼东西?!
What was that thing?!
救救我
我受伤了
它不见了  拜托
谁能救我
我们得进去救他
不行
No! no!
我受伤了  救救我
我不丢下任何人!
Do not leave anyone behind!
我们进去
不!  不!
No! no.
你不要去
You don't go.
你怀孕了
With baby.
不行
No.
怎么了?
What wrong?
把枪放下
Danielle  别这样  是我
你不是Robert  你变了
那个东西改变了你
求你了  Danielle
放下武器
我爱你  你怎么这样
因为你不是Robert  你病了
怪物使你染病了
我不是怪物
那是神殿的安全系统
现在...
把枪放下
我爱你  Danielle
我不会让任何事伤害...
你...
和我们的孩子
求你了...
别这样
别
No!
-是你  -别
-You! -no!
你消失了!
You disappeared!
不  等等!
No! please, wait!
你也病了  你是带菌者!  不!
You're sick, too! you're a carrier! no!
慢慢转过身去
Turn around slowly.
Jin?
Sawyer?
Jin!
没搞错吧!
You gotta be kiddin' me!
我以为你上船了  我以为你死了
I thought you were on that boat. I thought you were dead.
没  没有  我...掉水里了
No. no. i...in water.
真是不可思议啊
Well, what do you say?
Sun去哪了?
Where is sun?
那家伙从哪冒出来的?  我以为他在船上呢
Where did that guy come from? I thought he was on the boat.
肯定是爆炸把他炸到海里去了
The blast must've thrown him in the water.
他也像我们一样  穿梭时空
He's been moving with every flash, just like us.
每次天空闪亮时
Every time the sky lights up,
我们就...穿梭时空了
We...move through time.
翻译
Translate.
求你了  翻译
Please. translate.
你听到他的话了  翻译啊
You heard the man. translate.
拜托  他是韩国人  我又不是
Uh, he's korean. I'm from encino.
他想知道
He wants to know
你们怎么会肯定他老婆不在岛上
How you're sure his wife is off the island.
-你会说韩语?  -很明显嘛
-You speak korean, red? -obviously.
告诉他我能肯定  但是如果我们不去兰花站
Tell him I'm sure, but none of it will matter
就没用了
If we don't make it to the orchid.
他肯定  但是他说...
我们得回到那个兰花站
什么兰花站?
在岛的的另外一边
Locke计划离开这里...
去带回所有离开的人
包括你妻子
他认为这是唯一停止穿梭的办法
把Sun带回来?
Bring sun back?
为什么要带她回来?
Why you bring her back?
因为她原本就不该离开
Because she never should have left.
我花了三年的时间...
I've spent the last three years thinking...
来相信他已经死了
Believing that he was dead.
你却说你能证明他没死  证明给我看
You say you have proof that he's not. I want to see it.
何不先放下枪?  没人希望它走火
Why don't you put down the gun? no one wants it to go off.
你怎么知道他还活着?!
How do you know he's alive?!
某人...
there's someone...
某人在洛杉矶
Someone here in los angeles.
让我带你过去  然后我会证明给你看
Let me take you to them, and I'll show you the proof.
"某人"?  是谁?  同样是一个
"someone"? who? the same person
要带你们回岛上去的人
That's gonna shows how to get back to the island.
原来是这样?
Is that what this is about?
-你早就知道了?  -不不 我...
-You knew about this? -no. no, I was...
所以你才会假装关心Aaron
And that is why you were pretending to care about Aaron,
-来说服我回去?!  -我没有假装任何事
-To convince me to go back there?! -I wasn't pretending anything.
-真是疯了  你们都发疯了  -Kate...
-This is insane. you guys are crazy. -Kate...
Jack  别说了!
Jack, don't!
Sayid  你去哪里?
Sayid, where are you going?
我不想这样做  如果我再看到你或他
I don't want any part of this. and if I see you or him again?
我们都会非常不愉快
It'll be extremely unpleasant for all of us.
Sun  只要30分钟
30 minutes, sun.
30分钟我们就能到那
We can be there in 30 minutes.
我就能证明...证明他活着
And you'll have proof...proof that he's alive.
不然你就杀了我  永远都不知道他是死是活
Or you can shoot me and never know.
走吧
Let's go.
还有多远?
How far?
过下座桥就到了
It's just over the next ridge.
-你打算如何离开那岛?  -我还不知道
-How you will leave the island? -I'm not sure yet.
-我和你一起去  -不不  不能这样
-I go with you. -no, no. it doesn't work like that.
-只要一个人就行了  -为什么?
-It's a 1-man job. -why?
我不知道为什么  Jin  但必须这样
I don't know why, Jin. it just is.
我保证我会带Sun回来的
But I promise I'll bring sun back.
你没事吧?
You okay?
要休息一会吗?
You wanna take a break?
还是快点去吧
let's just get there.
好的
Yeah.
那个...
So, uh...
你还会讲其它语言吗?
You speak any other languages?
只会讲克林贡语
Just klingon.
Dan  这行得通吗?
Dan, is this gonna work?
从经验来讲应该可以
It...it does make empirical sense
如果一切是从兰花站开始
That if this started at the orchid,
那么也就应该可以结束这一切
Then that's where it's gonna stop.
但是至于把离开的人带回来
But as far as bringing back people who left
为了停止这些暂时错乱
In order to stop these temporal shifts,
那就没任何科学依据了
That's where we leave science behind.
你没事吧?
You okay?
不是吧
Oh, no!
搞什么
Come on!
Charlotte!
-Charlotte   -Juliet
-怎么?  -你也有点...
-Huh? -you have a little...
你也是
You, too.
Charlotte!
能听到我说话吗?  Charlotte?
Can you hear me? Charlotte?
能听到吗?
Can you hear me?
Charlotte? char...
她说什么?
What'd she say?
别让他们带她回来
Don't let them bring her back,
不管怎样
No matter what.
别让他们带她回来
Don't let them bring her back.
这是个死亡之岛
This place is death.
你说30分钟就到了
You said we'd be there in 30 minutes.
我没算交通堵塞时间
I didn't account for traffic.
Sun  对不起
Sun, I'm sorry.
对不起什么?
Sorry for what?
扔下Jin不管
For leaving Jin behind.
我们将直升机降落在船上的时候...
When we landed that chopper on the boat...
一切都发生的太快
Everything was just happening so fast.
我知道他在下面  但我...
I knew he was down below, but i...
我应该等他的
Should've waited for him.
Jack  你干嘛和我说这些?
Why are you telling me this now, jack?
你是要问我是否会杀了Ben
Are you going to ask me not to kill ben
如果他骗了我?
If he's lying about my husband?
他这样对Kate  就算你不杀他  我也会
After what he just did to Kate, if you don't do it, sun, I will.
你干嘛?!
What are you doing?!
我是在帮助你们
What I'm doing is helping you.
如果你们知道我做的一切都是为了
And if you had any idea what I've had to do
让你们安全  让你们的朋友们安全
To keep you safe, to keep your friends safe,
你们都不知道该如何感谢我
You'd never stop thanking me.
你想开枪吗  那就开吧
You wanna shoot me? then shoot me!
但我们最好还是快去
But let's get on with it.
怎么样?
What's it gonna be?
开车
Drive.
为什么爸爸不跟我们一起
Why can't daddy come with us?
Charlotte  能听见我说话吗
Charlotte, can you hear me?
你知道我妈妈会说什么吗
You know what my mum would say
关于我要嫁给美国人
About me marrying an american?
我比Hannibal知道古代Carthage更多
Yeah, I know more about ancient carthage than hannibal himself.
她到底在说什么
What the hell is she talking about?
不知道
Have no idea.
我们走  得继续赶路
Let's go. we have to keep moving.
好吧  谁和我帮Charlotte
All right, somebody help me with Charlotte.
-我们得带着她  -不  她会成为我们的负担
-We're gonna have to carry her, -no. she's gonna hold us up.
-我们不能扔下她  -闪光越来越频繁了
-We...we can't just leave her. -the flashes are getting closer together.
或许你流鼻血的时候
Maybe when your nose starts bleeding,
你会觉得我们应该放下负担
You'll realize we gotta get out of dodge now.
-等有机会再回来找她  -不  不行
-We'll come back for her just as soon as we can. -no. no way.
我们不能扔下她
We're not gonna leave her behind.
Daniel  让他们走吧
Let them go without me, daniel.
不  Charlotte  我不会扔下你的
No, Charlotte. no. I'm not gonna leave you behind.
怎么回事?!
the hell?!
-我们得马上走  -他是对的  走吧
-We have to move now! -he's right. go.
-Charlotte  -快走
-Charlotte...-just...no, just go!
Charlotte...
快开电视
Ohh! oh, turn it up.
我喜欢Geronimo Jackson
I love Geronimo Jackson.
Dan  没时间了
We're running out of time, Dan.
我会留下来陪着她
I'm gonna stay with her.
John  我来问你
Let me ask you something, John.
如果我们不知道我们到底在什么时代
If we don't even know when the hell we are.
如果兰花站不在了该怎么办
What happens if the orchid ain't around anymore?
去找那口井
Look for the well.
你会在井那找到的
You'll find it at the well.
好的  我们肯定会照做的
Yeah, we'll be sure and do that.
我们走
Let's go.
我们到了
We're here.
谢天谢地  太好了
Thank god. what are the odds
它还在这里
That we would end up in the same time as this thing?
你还真是乌鸦嘴
You just had to say somethin'.
Charlotte咋会知道这里有口井的?
How the hell did Charlotte know this was here?
-Daniel  -怎么了
-Daniel? -yes?
我以前来过这
I've been here before.
你以前来过这?
You've been...you've been here before?
我在岛上长大
I grew up here, on the island.
有这么一个组织...
Mm, there was this thing...
达摩组织
The Dharma initiative.
后来我跟我妈妈离开了
And then I moved away with my mum.
只跟我妈妈
Just my mom,
我再也没见过我爸爸
And I never saw my dad again.
我回到英国的时候
And then when I got back to england,
向我妈妈问起这地方的时候
W-when I would ask my mum about this place, yeah?
她说这不是真的  都是我编出来的
But she would say that it wasn't real and that I'd made it up.
那就是为什么我成了一位人类学家...
That's why...I became an anthropologist...
为了再找到这座岛
To find this island again.
我一生都在找这座岛
It's what I've been searching for my whole life.
Charlotte...
为什么你要告诉我这些
Why are you telling me this?
因为我现在想起一些事情
Because I remember something now.
我小的时候...
When I was little...
住在这里
Living here,
有这么个人...
There was this man...
一个疯子...他真的把我吓到了
A crazy man...he really scared me.
他告诉我  我必须要离开这座岛...
And he told me that I had to leave the island...
再也不能回来
And never, ever come back.
他跟我说
He told me
如果我回来的话
That if I came b-back,
我就会死
I would die.
Charlotte...
我不明白
I don't understand.
Daniel.
我...我想那个人就是你
I...I think that man was you.
你准备下去?
You're going down there?
你到底想找到些什么?
What exactly are you hoping to find?
找到离开小岛的办法
A way off the island.
不会是指望有地铁吧?
You expecting a subway?
再见了  James
Good-bye, James.
Juliet  Miles
回见了
I'll see you when I get back.
不  等等
No. stop.
别带Sun回来
You don't bring sun back.
不行  我得带所有人回来
No, I have to bring them all back.
因为必须这么做
That's...that's how it works.
你怎么知道?
How you know?
我...我就是知道
I-i...I just know.
-我会割断这个  -别  这样我们都会死
-I will cut this. -no. you do that, you'll kill every one of us.
这小岛不好  别带Sun回来  你发誓
This island is bad. you don't bring sun back. you promise.
发誓你不会带我孩子来!
You promise you don't bring my baby!
好的  好的  我答应你
All right. all right. you have my word.
John  你要发誓
Promise, John.
我发誓
I promise.
我不去找Sun  但她可能会找到我
I won't go to sun, Jin, but she might find me.
如果她找到我  我怎么说?
If she does, what do I tell her?
你告诉她  我死了
You tell her I'm dead.
你说我淹死了
You say I wash up.
是你埋的我
You burry me.
证据
Proof.
我会尽快回来
I'll be back as soon as I can.
你确定不要我们放你下去?
You sure you don't want us to lower you down?
这样的话  就不好玩啦
Where would be the fun in that?
John.
如果你做的这些  管用了的话
If whatever you're attempting to do actually works,
谢谢你了
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
不会吧?!
What?!
John  妈的  撑住!
John! damn it, hold on!
我想你可以放下手里的东西了
I think you can let go of that now.
不行
No.
-不  不  -James  算了
No! no! James, stop.
No! no! James, stop
快点来帮我
Come on and help me!
James.
我们帮不了他
We can't help him.
撑着  撑着
hold on. hold on.
撑下去
Stay. sta...stay with me.
就这样待着  好吗?
just stay, okay?
你会没事的  一切都会没事的
You're gonna be fine. everything's gonna be okay.
我有个计划
I've got a plan.
当我们回到那个舱门时  我告诉Desmond
When we were back at the hatch, I talked to Desmond.
让他去找我妈妈
I told him to find my mother.
她能帮助我们的  Charlotte
She can help us, Charlotte.
她会帮助我们的
She will help us.
你妈妈怎么帮我们?
How can your mother help us?
她能  她...
She can. she...
-听着  听着  -嗯?
-Hey, hey. listen, listen. -yeah?
什么?
What?
他们不准我饭前吃巧克力的
I'm not allowed to have chocolate before dinner.
Charlotte?
Charlotte.
不
No.
James!
能听到我说话吗?!
Can you hear me?!
有人听到我说话吗?!
Can anyone hear me?!
谁在那?
Who's there?
你好啊  John
Hello, John.
是你?
You?
你到下面来干嘛?
What are you doing down here?
我来助你一臂之力
I'm here to help you the rest of the way.
我不...我不懂
I don't...I don't understand.
上次你来小屋来我时
You came to see me in the cabin.
问我该如何救这个小岛
You asked me how to save the island,
我告诉你应该移动它
And I told you you had to move it.
我说是你来移动它  John
I said that you had to move it, John.
可是Ben说他知道如何移动
But ben said he knew how to do it.
他说我应该待在这里  领导他的人
He told me that I had to stay here and lead his people.
从什么时候开始
And since when did listening to him
你听信他的谗言了?
Get you anywhere worth a damn?
不过好消息是...
The good news...
现在你来这里了
Is that you're here now.
你准备好出发了吗?
Are you ready to go?
我...我不知道...
I-i d...i don't know...
我到了那里之后  该怎么做
what to do once I get there.
有个住在洛杉矶的女人
There's a woman living in los angeles.
等你朋友都聚齐之后...
And once you get all of your friends together...
一定要聚齐所有离开的人
And it must be all of them, everyone who left.
一旦你说服他们加入你之后...
And once you've persuaded them to join you...
这个女人会告诉你如何回来
This woman will tell you exactly how to come back.
谁...她是谁?
Who...who is she?
她叫Eloise Hawking
Her name is eloise hawking.
如果我只能说服部分人回来呢?
What if can only convince some of them to come back?
John  我相信你能的
I believe in you, John.
你能做到的
You can do this.
Richard说我要去死
Richard said I was going to die.
我想这就是...
Well, I suppose that's...
为什么他们称之为牺牲
That's why they call it sacrifice.
好吧
All right.
好 好了  我准备好了
Okay. oh, yeah, I'm ready.
很好
Good.
现在...
Now...
在隧道另一头
On the other side of this column here
有个从轴上松脱的转轮
Is a wheel that slipped off its axis.
你要做的就是稍微推它一下
And all you have to do is give it a little push.
你...你能帮我一把吗?
Could...could you help me up?
不能
No.
对不起  我不能
Sorry, I can't.
祝你好运  John
Good luck, John.
和我儿子打个招呼
Say hello to my son.
谁是你儿子?
Who's your son?
可以吗?
May i?
拿着
Take it.
你怎么有这个的?
How do you have this?
-John给我的  -你说John从没找过你
-John gave it to me. -you said John never came to see you.
没错  Jack  是我去找的他
That's true, jack. I went to see him.
在他离开岛之前  Jin给他的
Jin gave it to him before he left the island.
为什么Locke不亲自给我?
Why didn't locke tell me himself?
我不知道  可能在他死前 一直没机会告诉你吧
I don't know. maybe he never had a chance before he died.
对不起  在我给这个你之前
I'm sorry I had to bring you here
我必须带你来这  Sun
Before I gave it to you, sun.
可是留在岛上的人  包括Jin
But all those people back on the island, Jin included,
都需要我们的帮助
Need our help.
这座教堂里有个女人
There is a woman in this church,
她能告诉我们  如何带回你的丈夫
And she can tell us how to get back to your husband.
可是我们时间不多了  Sun
But we're running out of time, sun,
你必须马上做出决定
I need you to decide right now.
你会跟我一起去吗?
Will you come with me?
会
Yes.
你们来这干嘛?
What are you doin' here?
和你来的目的一样
I assume the same thing you are.
你们也在找Faraday的妈妈?
You're looking for Faraday's mother, too?
你好  Eloise
Hello, eloise.
你好  Benjamin
Hello, Benjamin.
我记得说过要带所有人来
I thought i said all of them.
目前就说服了这些  Eloise
This is all i can get on sure now,eloise
看来只能我出马了
Well, i suppose that i have to do from now on.
好吧
All right.
我们开始吧
Let's get started.